[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The loss of a single pawn is not enough to lose a chess game.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie The Great Escape, James Garner played Lt. Hendley. What was the character referred to as?", "correct_answer": "The Scrounger", "incorrect_answers": ["Big K", "Intelligence", "The Forger"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Whose body was replaced in the 2004 Remastered DVD at the very end of The Return of the Jedi?", "correct_answer": "Anakin Skywalkers", "incorrect_answers": ["Obi Wan Kenobis", "Emperor Palpetines", "Mace Windus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the longest river in Asia, and the third-longest in the world?", "correct_answer": "The Yangtze", "incorrect_answers": ["The Mekong-Lancang", "The Tigris", "The Huang He"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor portrayed the leading character Trooper William Billy Costigan, Jr. in Martin Scorseses 2006 crime movie The Departed?", "correct_answer": "Leonardo DiCaprio", "incorrect_answers": ["Robert De Niro", "Ben Affleck", "Mel Gibson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these deserts is largest?", "correct_answer": "Syrian", "incorrect_answers": ["Chihuahuan", "Thar", "Great Sandy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In this country people drink gorilka. It is similar to vodka.", "correct_answer": "Ukraine", "incorrect_answers": ["Georgia", "Azerbaijan", "Belarus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In The Color Purple, Oprah Winfreys character Shug Avery, helps Miss Celie cope with life as a black woman in the 1930s in the deep south.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Should I eat before taking my medication, if the prescription says the medication should be taken a.c.?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the two types of Chinese Crested dogs.", "correct_answer": "Hairless and Powderpuff", "incorrect_answers": ["Water and Runner", "Hairless and Hound", "Sporty and Spotted"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This type of macaroni is formed in a spiral tube shape an typically has lines on the outside surface.", "correct_answer": "cavatappi", "incorrect_answers": ["lumache", "lumaconi", "cavatelli"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When did Ireland join the European Union?", "correct_answer": "1973", "incorrect_answers": ["1995", "1960", "1986"]}]